export const Questions = [
  {
    "question": "In the 2010 census, how many US cities (not metro areas) had a population greater than 1 million?",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the shortest straight line distance in miles between two US state capitals?",
    "answer": 41
  },
  {
    "question": "In millions, what is the largest number of votes ever cast for a US Presidential candidate in a single election (through the 2016 election)?",
    "answer": 69.49
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did the US flag get its 25th star?",
    "answer": 1836
  },
  {
    "question": "How many different US states have national parks (as of the end of 2019)?",
    "answer": 29
  },
  {
    "question": "In feet, what is the difference between the highest and lowest elevations in the state of Florida?",
    "answer": 345
  },
  {
    "question": "How many US state capitals lie to the west of Los Angeles, CA or to the east of Miami, FL?",
    "answer": 19
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the highest temperature (in Fahrenheit) ever recorded in the US (as of 2019)?",
    "answer": 134.1
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the US Department of the Interior in 2012, what percent of the land in the US is owned by the federal government?",
    "answer": 28
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the first year in the 20th century in which a name besides Mary was the most popular name for new baby girls in the US? (replaced by the name Linda)",
    "answer": 1947
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the length (in miles) of the border between the US and Mexico?",
    "answer": 1989
  },
  {
    "question": "As of 2016, what is the median age of the US population?",
    "answer": 37.9
  },
  {
    "question": "Including the names of the signers, how many words are in the US Declaration of Independence?",
    "answer": 1458
  },
  {
    "question": "How many US states do not have any letters in their name that are used more than once?",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did China become the first country with a population greater than 1 billion?",
    "answer": 1982
  },
  {
    "question": "The largest earthquake ever recorded in the world was in Chile in 1960. What was the magnitude of this earthquake on the Richter scale?",
    "answer": 9.5
  },
  {
    "question": "In feet, what was the original width of the lock chambers in the Panama Canal?",
    "answer": 110
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the United Nations, what percent of the world's population lived in urban areas in 2014?",
    "answer": 54
  },
  {
    "question": "In millimeters, what did the 2013 Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change estimate as the average annual sea level rise?",
    "answer": 3.2
  },
  {
    "question": "How old was the oldest person to ever reach the summit of Mount Everest (as of 2017)?",
    "answer": 80
  },
  {
    "question": "How many countries have land that touches the equator (as of 2017)?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the largest combined score in any of the first 50 Super Bowls?",
    "answer": 75
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was the first electronically timed and officially recognized 100m sprint measured under 10 seconds?",
    "answer": 1968
  },
  {
    "question": "ESPN cable subscriptions have been declining as \"cord-cutting' has increased in popularity. What was their peak household subscriber count (in millions) in 2011?",
    "answer": 100.1
  },
  {
    "question": "As of 2019, how many US metropolitan areas had teams from all 4 major US sports leagues (NFL, NBA, MLB, NHL)?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "In whole dollars, what was the highest payout for a $2 bet on a winning horse in Kentucky Derby history (as of 2019)?",
    "answer": 184
  },
  {
    "question": "How many home runs were hit in Major League Baseball in 2000, the peak of the steroid era?",
    "answer": 5693
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 2016 Summer Olympics, how many different nations received gold medals?",
    "answer": 59
  },
  {
    "question": "Four new elements were added to the Periodic Table in 2015. What was the new total number of elements after that addition?",
    "answer": 118
  },
  {
    "question": "In seconds, how long does it take light from the sun to reach Earth?",
    "answer": 499
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of the first 1000 digits after the decimal point in pi?",
    "answer": 4476
  },
  {
    "question": "On average, how many times does the International Space Station circle the Earth every day?",
    "answer": 15.5
  },
  {
    "question": "Given a standard deck of cards (4 suits, 13 values), what is the percent chance that a random set of 5 cards contains exactly one pair and no better Poker hand?",
    "answer": 42.2
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did Sir Isaac Newton first publish his Principia, where he stated his laws of motion and gravitation?",
    "answer": 1687
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the 100th prime number?",
    "answer": 541
  },
  {
    "question": "As of 2007, what percent of the world's population lives in the US?",
    "answer": 4.57
  },
  {
    "question": "How many #1 singles did the Beatles have on the Billboard Hot 100 singles chart?",
    "answer": 21
  },
  {
    "question": "As of 2007, what percent of the world's population speaks Spanish as their first language?",
    "answer": 4.88
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2004, how many new SUVs were sold in the US?",
    "answer": 4623960
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 1961-62 NBA season, Wilt Chamberlain set the record for most points scored. How many points did he score per game?",
    "answer": 50.36
  },
  {
    "question": "How old was Nirvana lead singer Kurt Cobain when the group released their hit 1991 album Nevermind?",
    "answer": 24
  },
  {
    "question": "In millions, how many votes were cast to crown the 2007 American Idol on the TV show's 6th season finale?",
    "answer": 74
  },
  {
    "question": "Russia is the world's largest country. What percent of the world's total land area does Russia make up?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "How old was Martin Luther King, Jr. when he was assassinated in 1968?",
    "answer": 39
  },
  {
    "question": "The Pablo Picasso painting The Dream was purchased for $7,000 in 1941. In millions of dollars, how much was it sold for in 1997?",
    "answer": 48.4
  },
  {
    "question": "For how many months does the average US $1 bill stay in circulation?",
    "answer": 21
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was the Heisman Trophy first awarded to the best US college football player?",
    "answer": 1935
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Emmy nominations did Comedy Central's The Colbert Report receive for its first season?",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did explorer Ferdinand Magellan embark on the first successful attempt to sail around the world?",
    "answer": 1519
  },
  {
    "question": "34 million people lived in California in 2000. How many people lived in California in 1900?",
    "answer": 1485053
  },
  {
    "question": "How old was Joan of Arc when she was burned at the stake in 1431?",
    "answer": 19
  },
  {
    "question": "As of 2007, what percent of US residents are Caucasian?",
    "answer": 66.38
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2006, what percent of US adults had a member account at Blockbuster?",
    "answer": 49.93
  },
  {
    "question": "The are 58,249 names etched in the Vietnam Veterans Memorial Wall. How many are of women?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "In dollars, how much did a 3-day ticket to the original Woodstock concert cost at the gate?",
    "answer": 24
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was an ATM machine first installed in the US?",
    "answer": 1969
  },
  {
    "question": "How many miles long is the main wall of the Great Wall of China, excluding all of its secondary branches?",
    "answer": 4163
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the average age of US combat soldiers during the Vietnam War?",
    "answer": 19
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2006, what percent of US households subscribed to basic cable?",
    "answer": 83.96
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did IBM release its first personal computer?",
    "answer": 1981
  },
  {
    "question": "The record time for the Daytona 500 car race was set in 1980. In miles per hour, what was the winner's average speed?",
    "answer": 177.6
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did the radio presentation War of the Worlds cause a panic because many people thought that Martians were invading the Earth?",
    "answer": 1938
  },
  {
    "question": "Jupiter is the largest planet in our solar system. How many times larger in volume is Jupiter than the Earth?",
    "answer": 1321.33
  },
  {
    "question": "What percent of the Earth's water area does the Atlantic Ocean make up?",
    "answer": 21.26
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did the repeal of Prohibition make it legal once again to sell alcohol in the US?",
    "answer": 1933
  },
  {
    "question": "How many official languages are used by the United Nations?",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was penicillin, the first antibiotic, discovered?",
    "answer": 1928
  },
  {
    "question": "How many US $1 bills would be contained in a stack of bills one foot high?",
    "answer": 2746
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was the film Citizen Kane first released?",
    "answer": 1941
  },
  {
    "question": "How many artists made up USA for Africa, the group that recorded the 1985 hit song We Are the World?",
    "answer": 45
  },
  {
    "question": "Rhode Island is the smallest US state, while Alaska is the largest. How many Rhode Islands could fit into the land area of Alaska?",
    "answer": 546
  },
  {
    "question": "What percent of the US population disapproved of Richard Nixon's presidency in August 1974?",
    "answer": 66
  },
  {
    "question": "The world's population reached 1 billion in 1804. In what year did it reach 2 billion?",
    "answer": 1927
  },
  {
    "question": "The femur is the longest bone in the human body. On average, how many inches long is this bone in an adult male?",
    "answer": 19.88
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the record for most touchdowns scored by a single player in an NFL season?",
    "answer": 31
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was the Atari 2600 video game system first sold in the US?",
    "answer": 1977
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year were African-Americans in the US granted the right to vote?",
    "answer": 1870
  },
  {
    "question": "In miles, how wide is the English Channel at its narrowest point?",
    "answer": 21
  },
  {
    "question": "How many speaking roles were there in The Lord of the Rings movie trilogy?",
    "answer": 114
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did Rapper's Delight become the first rap song to enter the Billboard Top 40 chart?",
    "answer": 1979
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Category 5 hurricanes hit the US during the 20th century?",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "10,500 athletes competed in the 2004 Summer Olympics. How many were expelled for drug violations?",
    "answer": 24
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did rockers Buddy Holly, Ritchie Valens, and the Big Bopper die in a plane crash following a concert?",
    "answer": 1959
  },
  {
    "question": "What percent of the Earth's water area does the Pacific Ocean make up?",
    "answer": 43.07
  },
  {
    "question": "What percent of US land area does Texas make up?",
    "answer": 7.4
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was an African-American first appointed to the US cabinet?",
    "answer": 1966
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2007, how many hours per week did the average American spend surfing the internet?",
    "answer": 28.51
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did a company first provide consumers with dial-up internet access?",
    "answer": 1989
  },
  {
    "question": "Wayne Gretzky holds the National Hockey League record for most career goals. How many goals did he average per season?",
    "answer": 42.57
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Grammy Awards did Elvis Presley win?",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was the novel Frankenstein first published?",
    "answer": 1818
  },
  {
    "question": "How many feet above sea level is the highest point on the world's tallest volcano?",
    "answer": 22615
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did the siege of the Alamo occur in Texas?",
    "answer": 1836
  },
  {
    "question": "How many spaces are there on a Trivial Pursuit board?",
    "answer": 73
  },
  {
    "question": "The Australian dragonfly is the fastest flying insect. In miles per hour, what is its average speed?",
    "answer": 24
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was Pete Rose banned from Major League Baseball?",
    "answer": 1989
  },
  {
    "question": "Jimi Hendrix's Fender Stratocaster electric guitar was auctioned in 1990. In dollars, what was the sale price?",
    "answer": 323522
  },
  {
    "question": "In millions, how many viewers watched the final episode of Seinfeld?",
    "answer": 76
  },
  {
    "question": "What percent of US land area does Alaska make up?",
    "answer": 16.17
  },
  {
    "question": "President Bush's 2007 State of the Union speech lasted 49 minutes. How many times was he interrupted by applause?",
    "answer": 58
  },
  {
    "question": "Before The Departed, how many full-length feature films did Martin Scorcese direct?",
    "answer": 25
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did the US Surgeon General first declare that cigarettes are addictive?",
    "answer": 1988
  },
  {
    "question": "Pete Rose holds the Major League Baseball record for most career hits. How many hits did he average per season?",
    "answer": 177.33
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did LEGO introduce its first building blocks?",
    "answer": 1949
  },
  {
    "question": "How many weeks did Michael Jackson's Thriller spend at #1 on the Billboard 200 album chart?",
    "answer": 37
  },
  {
    "question": "How many miles is it in a straight line between New York and Los Angeles?",
    "answer": 2462
  },
  {
    "question": "How many days passed between election night 2000 and Al Gore's final concession to George W. Bush?",
    "answer": 36
  },
  {
    "question": "What percent of the US federal prison population is imprisoned for drug offenses (as of 2007)?",
    "answer": 53.6
  },
  {
    "question": "How many miles does light travel in one second?",
    "answer": 186282
  },
  {
    "question": "How many touchdown passes did Joe Montana throw during his 15-year NFL career?",
    "answer": 273
  },
  {
    "question": "How many cards are in an original Uno deck?",
    "answer": 108
  },
  {
    "question": "In miles, what is the distance around the Earth at its equator?",
    "answer": 24902
  },
  {
    "question": "In feet, how deep is the world's deepest ocean trench?",
    "answer": 35840
  },
  {
    "question": "How many southern states joined the Confederacy during the US Civil War?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was a newspaper first published in the US?",
    "answer": 1690
  },
  {
    "question": "In days, what is the longest that any astronaut has spent in space on a single mission?",
    "answer": 437.75
  },
  {
    "question": "Cal Ripken, Jr. holds the Major League Baseball record for most consecutive games played. How many games did he play in a row?",
    "answer": 2632
  },
  {
    "question": "How many actresses have received Emmy nominations for their role on Desperate Housewives?",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "In miles per hour, what is the minimum wind speed necessary for a Category 5 hurricane?",
    "answer": 156
  },
  {
    "question": "In dollars, how much did the most expensive ticket cost on the Titanic in 1912?",
    "answer": 4350
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did Texas become a US state?",
    "answer": 1845
  },
  {
    "question": "How many years older is the Jewish calendar than the Christian calendar?",
    "answer": 3760
  },
  {
    "question": "How many years passed between the introduction of Coca-Cola and the introduction of Diet Coke?",
    "answer": 96
  },
  {
    "question": "The first Indianapolis 500 car race was held in 1911. In miles per hour, what was the average speed of the winner?",
    "answer": 74.6
  },
  {
    "question": "In dollars, how much was Margaret Mitchell paid for the rights to make her novel Gone with the Wind into a movie?",
    "answer": 50000
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did Washington, DC become the home of the US federal government?",
    "answer": 1800
  },
  {
    "question": "How many miles long is the Nile River?",
    "answer": 4160
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did Alexander Graham Bell receive a patent for the invention of the telephone?",
    "answer": 1876
  },
  {
    "question": "How many children's books did Dr. Suess write and illustrate?",
    "answer": 44
  },
  {
    "question": "How many glasses of milk does the average milk cow produce in a year?",
    "answer": 46000
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did a man first barrel over Niagara Falls and survive?",
    "answer": 1911
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2007, how many people on average watched CBS' The Early Show each day?",
    "answer": 3030000
  },
  {
    "question": "What percent of US credit card bills are paid in full each month (as of 2007)?",
    "answer": 55.3
  },
  {
    "question": "1.2 million people lived in Detroit in 1980. How many people lived in Detroit in 2005?",
    "answer": 886671
  },
  {
    "question": "In years, how old was Anna Nicole Smith when she died?",
    "answer": 39
  },
  {
    "question": "What percent of Americans age 18 to 29 have at least one tattoo (as of 2006)?",
    "answer": 36
  },
  {
    "question": "In miles per hour, how fast does sound travel at sea level?",
    "answer": 761
  },
  {
    "question": "How many touchdown passes did Dan Marino average per season?",
    "answer": 24.71
  },
  {
    "question": "How many times has actress Elizabeth Taylor been married?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was the US Social Security system created?",
    "answer": 1935
  },
  {
    "question": "What percent of US women are left-handed?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did Abraham Lincoln deliver the Gettysburg Address?",
    "answer": 1863
  },
  {
    "question": "What percent of US holiday shoppers expect at least one of their gifts to be returned (as of 2004)?",
    "answer": 56
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did Sally Ride become the first American woman to travel into space?",
    "answer": 1983
  },
  {
    "question": "In feet, how long is a regulation tennis court?",
    "answer": 78
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did Led Zeppelin first release the album Led Zeppelin IV, which contained the song Stairway to Heaven?",
    "answer": 1971
  },
  {
    "question": "How many bedrooms does Buckingham Palace have?",
    "answer": 240
  },
  {
    "question": "In inches, what is the standard distance between US railroad tracks?",
    "answer": 56.5
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did a US president first live in the White House?",
    "answer": 1800
  },
  {
    "question": "What percent of Americans watch the same movie each year as part of their Christmas holiday tradition?",
    "answer": 61
  },
  {
    "question": "In dollars, how much did the average gallon of gasoline cost in the US in 1980?",
    "answer": 1.22
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Olympic medals has track & field star Carl Lewis won?",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "Stevie Wonder was the youngest male soloist to have a #1 US single. How old was he when he achieved this feat?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was Rosa Parks arrested for refusing to give up her seat on a bus in Montgomery, Alabama?",
    "answer": 1955
  },
  {
    "question": "How many feet below sea level is the Dead Sea?",
    "answer": 1348
  },
  {
    "question": "How many pounds does the comic book character Wonder Woman weigh?",
    "answer": 165
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2006, how many emails were sent on an average day (in billions)?",
    "answer": 31
  },
  {
    "question": "If a person weighs 100 pounds on Earth, how many pounds would they weigh on the surface of the moon?",
    "answer": 16.5
  },
  {
    "question": "What percent of Americans find the commercials to be the most important part of the Super Bowl (as of 2007)?",
    "answer": 18.1
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did U2 first release the album Achtung Baby?",
    "answer": 1992
  },
  {
    "question": "How many gallons of water does it take to fill up an Olympic-size pool?",
    "answer": 800000
  },
  {
    "question": "2 John has the smallest number of verses in the New Testament. How many verses does it have?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "How old was Adam when he died?",
    "answer": 930
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Philistine foreskins did Saul require David to obtain before he would allow his daughter Michal to marry David?",
    "answer": 100
  },
  {
    "question": "How many verses does Psalms 119 have?",
    "answer": 176
  },
  {
    "question": "How many letters did Paul write in the New Testament? Note: Given that the author does not identify himself in the Book of Hebrews, it will be excluded from the answer.",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "How old was Noah when the Flood occurred?",
    "answer": 600
  },
  {
    "question": "How old was Abraham when his first son was born?",
    "answer": 86
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did Charles Dickens first publish the novel \"A Christmas Carol\"?",
    "answer": 1843
  },
  {
    "question": "In the movie \"A Christmas Story\" how many times does Ralphie say he wants a Red Ryder BB Gun?",
    "answer": 28
  },
  {
    "question": "What percent of Americans watch the same movie each year as part of their Christmas holiday tradition?",
    "answer": 61
  },
  {
    "question": "Suppose you got all the Christmas gifts from your true love, as the song goes in the 12 days of Christmas. How many gifts would you have?",
    "answer": 364
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was the electric holiday lighting first used during the U.S. Christmas season?",
    "answer": 1882
  },
  {
    "question": "On average, what percent of all U.S. holiday shopping is completed in the final week before Christmas?",
    "answer": 32
  },
  {
    "question": "The record for tallest Christmas tree was recorded in Milan, Italy, in December 2003. How tall (in feet) was the tree?",
    "answer": 334
  },
  {
    "question": "How many books are in Euclid's Elements?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "When did Immanuel Kant first publish The Critique of Pure Reason?",
    "answer": 1781
  },
  {
    "question": "The first influential novel, Don Quixote, was published in what year?",
    "answer": 1605
  },
  {
    "question": "For how many years is Odysseus stuck on Calypso's island?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "How many dialogues are in the \"The Collected Dialogues of Plato\"?",
    "answer": 28
  },
  {
    "question": "Excluding both of the epilogues, how many chapters are in Leo Tolstoy's novel War and Peace?",
    "answer": 337
  },
  {
    "question": "How many full-length plays did William Shakespeare write?",
    "answer": 37
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did the Council of Nicaea decide that all Christians must celebrate Easter on a Sunday?",
    "answer": 325
  },
  {
    "question": "In the West, what year was the last time Easter fell on March 22nd, the earliest possible day of year it can occur?",
    "answer": 1818
  },
  {
    "question": "In the West, what year was the last time Easter fell on April 25th, the latest possible day of year it can occur?",
    "answer": 1943
  },
  {
    "question": "How many jeweled eggs were made by Carl Fabergé and his assistants?",
    "answer": 69
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did Carl Fabergé make his first jeweled egg?",
    "answer": 1885
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was Christ crucified?",
    "answer": 30
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was the first White House lawn egg rolling contest held, traditionally on the Monday after Easter?",
    "answer": 1878
  },
  {
    "question": "Puerto Rico is the #1 ranked game on the Board Game Geek.  On May 1st 2006, how many ratings did Puerto Rico have on the Board Game Geek?",
    "answer": 5838
  },
  {
    "question": "On August 1st 2007, what was the ranking of Settlers Of Catan on the Board Game Geek?",
    "answer": 20
  },
  {
    "question": "On August 1st 2007, what was the ranking of Chess on the Board Game Geek?",
    "answer": 176
  },
  {
    "question": "On February 28th 2008, Wits & Wagers was ranked above Zooloretto and below Taluva.  What was its ranking on the Board Game Geek?",
    "answer": 172
  },
  {
    "question": "How many new Reiner Knizia publications are listed for 2005 on his homepage?",
    "answer": 97
  },
  {
    "question": "How many total wooden pieces are supposed to come in a game of Puerto Rico?",
    "answer": 150
  },
  {
    "question": "How many tiles (not including scoring tablets) are included in the original 1999 version of Ra?",
    "answer": 180
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was the Count Dracula Society formed?",
    "answer": 1962
  },
  {
    "question": "How many days did it take to film the movie \"Halloween\" in 1978?",
    "answer": 21
  },
  {
    "question": "How many millions of dollars do American candy companies earn from selling Halloween candy on average?",
    "answer": 2000
  },
  {
    "question": "How many pounds was the world's heaviest pumpkin?",
    "answer": 1385
  },
  {
    "question": "How many pounds of candy did the average American consume in 2002?",
    "answer": 24
  },
  {
    "question": "How old was Elvira, the Mistress of the Dark,  on September 17th, 2007?",
    "answer": 58
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was Frankenstein written by Mary Shelley?",
    "answer": 1818
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was the Pledge of Allegiance written?",
    "answer": 1892
  },
  {
    "question": "As of 2007, how many Indianapolis 500 races have been run?",
    "answer": 91
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was West Point founded?",
    "answer": 1802
  },
  {
    "question": "How many German soldiers did Sergeant York and his squad of 7 soldiers capture in 1918 in World War I?",
    "answer": 132
  },
  {
    "question": "How many people (in millions) died in World War I?",
    "answer": 20
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was the first day of rememberance of fallen soldiers held in the U.S.?",
    "answer": 1866
  },
  {
    "question": "How many names are on the the Vietnam Veteran's Memorial Wall?",
    "answer": 58195
  },
  {
    "question": "How old was Jeff Gordon during the 2007 Race for the Cup?",
    "answer": 36
  },
  {
    "question": "In inches, how tall is Jeff Gordon?",
    "answer": 67
  },
  {
    "question": "How many pounds does Jeff Gordon weight?",
    "answer": 150
  },
  {
    "question": "Kevin Harvick won the 2007 Daytona 500.  How many money did he win?",
    "answer": 1563470
  },
  {
    "question": "In what place did Jimmie Johnson finish the 2007 Daytona 500?",
    "answer": 37
  },
  {
    "question": "How many career wins did Jimmie Johnson have at the beginning of the 2007 season?",
    "answer": 23
  },
  {
    "question": "Jimmie Johnson won more money than any other NASCAR driver during the 2006 season.  How much money did he win?",
    "answer": 8909140
  },
  {
    "question": "How many people attended the St. Patrick's Day parade in Dublin, Ireland, in 2006?",
    "answer": 500000
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was the first St. Patrick's Day parade held in Boston?",
    "answer": 1737
  },
  {
    "question": "The famous blue Blarney Stone was set into Blarney Castle in what year?",
    "answer": 1446
  },
  {
    "question": "Women made up what percentage of drunk driver arrests in the U.S. in 2006?",
    "answer": 22
  },
  {
    "question": "How many people did St. Patrick baptize in his lifetime?",
    "answer": 120000
  },
  {
    "question": "How many calories in a 16 oz. McDonalds Shamrock Shake?",
    "answer": 580
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was St. Patrick born?",
    "answer": 385
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2005, how many turkeys (in millions) were killed for Thanksgiving meals?",
    "answer": 45
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2004, how many people (in millions) watched the Macy's Thanksgiving Day parade on television?",
    "answer": 44
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most helium (in cubic feet) ever used to inflate the Macy's Thanksgiving Day parade ballons?",
    "answer": 400000
  },
  {
    "question": "What year did the Pilgrims hold Thanksgiving with Native Americans for the first time?",
    "answer": 1621
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the Guinness Book of Records, the largest ever turkey raised was how many pounds?",
    "answer": 86
  },
  {
    "question": "How many professional football games have been played on Thanksgiving Day?",
    "answer": 191
  },
  {
    "question": "How many calories will the average American consume on Thanksgiving?",
    "answer": 4500
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Valentine's Day cards (in millions) were given worldwide in 2007?",
    "answer": 1000
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people who buy flowers for Valentine's Day are men?",
    "answer": 73
  },
  {
    "question": "What day of the year in 2008 do Japanese women give chocolate to men (e.g., Jan. 29 = 29)?",
    "answer": 74
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did the Valentine's Day Massacre occur?",
    "answer": 1929
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was Romeo and Juliet written?",
    "answer": 1595
  },
  {
    "question": "How many different Valentine's Day cards does Hallmark have?",
    "answer": 1330
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did St. Valentine die?",
    "answer": 269
  }
]